[{"answer": "Naw, it's okay", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Thanks. I'm obliged to ya, but I gotta get goin'.", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "It don't look good, gramps, it's ten of now", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " I dunno. That little mug that got ya is mad enough at me already", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I got a hundred bucks for you and your friend if you deliver the money for me", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "He won't know you're carryin' it. C'mon, you gotta help me out", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Hi, my friend, you gettin' married or somethin'", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Can't. I got a 10 o'clock show. I need the five bucks", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'm out, my friend", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "That's the way I want it", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You mean you blew it", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "He didn't tell me you was a fuc", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You can't do it alone, ya know. It takes a mob of guys like you and enough money to make 'em look good", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "This isn't like playin' winos on the street. You gotta do more than outrun the guy", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Raise 500", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " See and raise five", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You the Duff that didn't come up with his end when my friend was sent up", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He was a con man, wasn't he", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "250", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Raise 500", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You should always look to the back too, kid", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Get on with it then", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "All right, my friend. What the hell happened", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You weren't hired to miss him", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You're a lucky man, all right", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Why don't ya then", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You got a system, my friend", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm in", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why don't you pick him up yourself", "docId": "Sting_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Wouldn't that be too bad. You'd hafta move outa this nice office ya got", "qsentId": 30}]